http://www.thescreenmachine.com/privacy-policy/

Screen Machine Industries Privacy Policy - Screen Machine Industries
Search for:
Search
Search for:
SearchHomeEquipmentDownload BrochuresEquipment VideosCrushing Plants5256T Impact Crusher4043T Impact Crusher4043TR Recirculating Impact CrusherJXT Jaw CrusherJHT Jaw CrusherCST Cone CrusherCXT Cone CrusherScreening PlantsSpyder 622TH Triple Deck ScreenSpyder 520TS3 ScreenSpyder 516T ScreenSpyder 514TS3 Triple Deck ScreenSpyder 514TS ScreenScalper 107T ScreenScalper 107D ScreenScalper 77C ScreenTrommel Screens621ST Shredder612T Trommel Screen612W Trommel ScreenMight II Trommel/ShredderRadial Conveyors80 Foot Radial Conveyor60 Foot Tracked Conveyor60 Foot Radial Conveyor50 Foot Radial Conveyor40 Foot Radial Conveyor30 Foot Radial ConveyorSMI CompactDealer InventoryIndustry ApplicationsAggregate MiningConstruction RecyclingDemolition RecyclingTopsoil ScreensCompost & Mulch ScreensContactDealer LocatorRequest Machine PricingBecome A DealerParts DepartmentWarranty RegistrationsService Cases / Warranty ClaimsRequest Dealer Portal AccessAboutWhere to Buy SMI ProductsOur Vision, Our MissionOur Value PropositionEngineering CapabilitiesManufacturing CapabilitiesSMI CareersSMI on Social MediaFacebookTwitterYouTubeLinkedinDealersOpen Mobile MenuPrivacy PolicyHome » Privacy PolicyThank you for visiting screenmachine.com, a SCREEN MACHINE INDUSTRIES LLC. web site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site.The Information We CollectAt our site, you can subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.At our site, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send product information and you might submit the recipient’s name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows, Mac OS, Linux, etc) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink) and IP.How We Use the InformationWe may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for Equipment Lines, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them literature. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer Equipment Lines, programs, or services to them.We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.Agents and contractors of The Screen Machine® who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for The Screen Machine®.Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.If The Screen Machine® discloses personally identifiable information to companies not owned by Screen Machine Industries who want to market products or services to you, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses.Finally, The Screen Machine® will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and SponsorsIf our site contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.The Screen Machine® sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or cosponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. The Screen Machine® has no control over the third-party sponsors’ use of this information. The Screen Machine® will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.CookiesTo enhance your experience with our site, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages, save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. Cookies also let us know how you found us (e.g., through a particular web site or advertisement).Our Commitment to SecurityWe have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.Get in Touchemail@screenmachine.com
10685 Columbus Parkway
Etna, Ohio 43062
1-800-837-3344 (in USA)
Dealer Portal | SMI Webmail | SMI Terms of Sale | Legal | Privacy Policy
Back to top
